let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Who won the most IPL titles?",
        option: [
            "CSK",
            "MI",
            "RCB",
            "KKR",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who won the world cup 2019?",
        option: [
            "India",
            "Pakistan",
            "England",
            "Bangladesh",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who hit 4 centuries in single IPL match?",
        option: [
            "Virat Kohli",
            "MS Dhoni",
            "Rohit sharma",
            "Nicholas pooran",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Who won world cup more than four times?",
        option: [
            "Australia",
            "England",
            "Pakistan",
            "India",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Who is the bowler not in Dinda academy?",
        option: [
            "Umesh Yadav",
            "Mohd. Siraj",
            "Washington sundar",
            "Basil Thampi",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who won the man of the series award in 2011WC?",
        option: ["Harbhajan Singh", "Suresh Raina", "Piyush Chawla", "Yuvraj singh"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many times RCB won IPL trophy?",
        option: [
            "Zero",
            "One",
            "Two",
            "Three",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "From the below options, Who is not the net bowler for Border Gavaskar troph 2020-2021?",
        option: ["Thangarasu natarajan", "Ishan Porel", "Navdeep Saini", "kamalesh Nagarkoti"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "In which TNPL-Tamil Nadu Premier League Started? ",
        option: ["2018", "2019", "2017", "2016"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "From the below players,who is the player represented for two Countries?",
        option: ["Luke Ronchi", "Mitchel Johnson", "Michael Holding", "Mutaiah Muralidaran"],
        answer: 1,
    },
	{
        question: "From the below players,who is the player represented for two Countries?",
        option: ["Luke Ronchi", "Mitchel Johnson", "Michael Holding", "Mutaiah Muralidaran"],
        answer: 1,
    },
];
